♪ HEY, YEAH ♪
♪ I WANNA SHOOP, BABY ♪
♪ SHOOP ♪
♪ OH, HOW YOU DOIN', BABY ♪
♪ NO, NOT YOU ♪
♪ YOU, THE BOW-LEGGED
ONE, YEAH ♪
♪ WHAT'S YOUR NAME ♪
♪ SHOOP ♪
♪ DAMN, THAT SOUNDS SEXY ♪
♪ HERE I GO, HERE I
GO, HERE I GO AGAIN ♪
♪ GIRLS, WHAT'S MY WEAKNESS ♪
♪ MEN ♪
♪ OK THEN, CHILLIN', CHILLIN',
MINDIN' MY BUSINESS
(WORD) ♪
♪ YO, SALT, I LOOKED AROUND,
AND I COULDN'T BELIEVE THIS ♪
♪ I SWEAR, I STARED,
MY NIECE MY WITNESS ♪
♪ THE BROTHER HAD IT GOIN'
ON WITH SOMETHIN' KINDA, UH ♪
♪ WICKED, WICKED,
HAD TO KICK IT ♪
♪ I'M NOT SHY SO I
ASKED FOR THE DIGITS ♪
♪ A HOE, NO, THAT
DON'T MAKE ME ♪
♪ SEE WHAT I WANT SLIP
SLIDE TO IT SWIFTY ♪
♪ FELT IT IN MY HIPS SO I DIPPED
BACK TO MY BAG OF TRICKS ♪
♪ THEN I FLIPPED FOR A TIP, MAKE
ME WANNA DO TRICKS FOR HIM ♪
♪ LICK HIM LIKE A LOLLIPOP
SHOULD BE LICKED ♪
♪ CAME TO MY SENSES AND
I CHILLED FOR A BIT ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO
THE VOODOO THAT YOU DO ♪
♪ SO WELL IT'S A SPELL ♪
♪ HELL, MAKES ME WANNA
SHOOP SHOOP SHOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ UM, YOU'RE PACKED
AND YOU'RE STACKED ♪
♪ 'SPECIALLY IN THE BACK ♪
♪ BROTHER, WANNA
THANK YOUR MOTHER
FOR A BUTT LIKE THAT ♪
♪ (THANKS, MOM)
CAN I GET SOME FRIES WITH
THAT SHAKE-SHAKE BOOTY ♪
♪ IF LOOKS COULD KILL
YOU WOULD BE AN THAN ♪
♪ YOU'RE A SHOTGUN, BANG ♪
♪ WHAT'S UP WITH THAT THANG ♪
♪ I WANNA KNOW
HOW DOES IT HANG ♪
♪ STRAIGHT UP, WAIT UP,
HOLD UP, MR. LOVER ♪
♪ LIKE PRINCE SAID
YOU'RE A SEXY MOTHER ♪
♪ WELL I LIKE 'EM REAL WILD,
B-BOY STYLE BY THE MILE ♪
♪ SMOOTH BLACK
SKIN WITH A SMILE ♪
♪ BRIGHT AS THE SUN, I
WANNA HAVE SOME FUN ♪
♪ COME AND GIVE ME SOME OF
THAT YUM-YUM CHOCOLATE CHIP ♪
♪ HONEY DIP, CAN I
GET A SCOOP, PLEASE ♪
♪ BABY, TAKE A RIDE IN MY
COUPE, YOU MAKE ME WANNA ♪
♪ SHOOP SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ BABY, HEY ♪
♪ (SHOOP BA-DOOP)
SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW I
WANNA SHOOP, BABY ♪
♪ SHOOP, SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ WELL LET ME BRING YOU
BACK TO THE SUBJECT
PEP'S ON THE SET ♪
♪ MAKE YOU GET HOT, MAKE
YOU WORK UP A SWEAT ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SKIP-TO-MY-LOU,
MY DARLING ♪
♪ NOT FALLING IN LOVE
BUT I'M FALLING FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN I GET YA
BETCHA BOTTOM DOLLAR ♪
♪ YOU WERE BEST UNDER PRESSURE ♪
- YO, SANDY, I WANNA
LIKE, TASTE YOU.
♪ BETCHA GETCHA LIPS WET
CUZ IT'S TIME TO HAVE PEP ♪
♪ ON YOUR MARK, GET SET, GO,
LET ME GO, LET ME SHOOP ♪
♪ TO THE NEXT MAN IN
THE THREE-PIECE SUIT ♪
♪ I SPEND ALL MY
DOUGH, RAY ME, CUTIE ♪
♪ SHOOP SHOOP A-DOOBIE
LIKE SCOOBIE DOOBIE DOO ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU IN YOUR BIG JEANS,
YOU GIVE ME NICE DREAMS ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME WANNA SCREAM,
"OOOO, OOOO, OOOO!" ♪
♪ I LIKE WHAT YA DO
WHEN YOU DO WHAT YA DO ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME WANNA SHOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
- OH, MY GOODNESS,
GIRL, LOOK AT HIM!
HE'S THE CUTEST BROTHER IN HERE
AND HE'S COMIN' THIS WAY! OOOO!
♪ S AND THE P WANNA
KICK WITH ME, COOL ♪
♪ BUT I'M WICKED, G ♪
♪ HIT SKINS BUT NEVER QUICKLY ♪
♪ I HIT THE SKINS
FOR THE HELL OF IT
JUST FOR THE YELL I GET ♪
♪ MM MM MM, FOR
THE SMELL OF IT ♪
♪ THEY WANT MY BOD,
HERE'S THE HOT ROD ♪
♪ TWELVE INCHES TO A YARD ♪
♪ AND HAVE YA SOUNDIN' LIKE A ♪
♪ BIG 'TWAN LOVE-HER,
SIX-TWO, WANNA HIT YOU ♪
♪ SO WHAT YOU WANNA DO ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANNA DO ♪
♪ MM, I WANNA SHOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ SHOOP BA-DOOP
SHOOP BA-DOOP
BA-DOOP BA-DOOP ♪
♪ OH YOU MAKE ME WANNA SHOOP ♪
♪ HEY YEAH, I
WANNA SHOOP, BABY ♪